# **Gregory Tang**

## Software Engineer at Wavely

**Phone:** 5129662477

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gregory-tang-041127153

Email: gtang159@gmail.com

I am an active learner currently working as a full-time software engineer. I am passionate towards creating full-stack applications and flawless user experiences for individuals. I possess strong organizational and people skills, as well as technical skills which range from front-end web development with React.js and Node.js to prototyping and wire-framing with Figma.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Wavely August 2019 - Present

#### Software Engineering Intern

- Use React.js/Vue.js, HTML5, and CSS3/Flexbox, as well as collaborate with designers to create and update Wavely landing page, blog page, and about page.
- Use Express.js and Node.js to create backend with a REST api for Wavely blog page
- Configured Wavely blog page and about page to be hosted on apache servers with a distributed LAMP stack
- Created dynamic meta tags for technical SEO
- Currently creating a dashboard to consolidate iOS and Android download data using React.js and apple store/google play api.

Virta Health

November 2018 - August 2019

#### Office Manager

- Work cross-functionally with UXD and Engineering team members to integrate a food guide into our mobile app, which led to a 5% increase in patient success rate
- Assisted our Clinical Team with integrating search bar functionality in our internal health coach app, which reduced wasted search time by 20%

#### **EDUCATION**

# **UC Berkeley Extension**

February 2019 - August 2019

#### Full-stack Software Development

Locals - Web application built upon the MVC framework that allows travelers to connect and book Locals in a particular area for guided tours and events.

- Frontend: React.js, CSS3/Flexbox, HTML5
- Backend/Database: Node.js, Express, MongoDB

Tranquil - Web Application built upon the MVC framework that aims to reduce stress for users by giving them a stress score, as well as suggestions on videos they can watch.

- Frontend: Materialize/CSS3, HTML5, Vanilla.js, Handlebars .
- Backend/Database: Node.js, Express, MySQL

Swolemates - Web Application that matches users with gym buddies based off of their user preferences.

- Frontend: Bootstrap4, Vanilla.js/JQuery, CSS3/Flexbox
- Backend/Database: Firestore, Firebase

Github Link: https://github.com/Tangerinez?tab=repositories

UC Berkeley

August 2014 - May 2018

## Moelcular and Cellular Biology

#### **SKILLS**

Technical: React.js, Vue.js, Express.js, Node.js, Bootstrap4/React-strap, HTML5, CSS3/Flexbox, MySQL, MongoDB, Git Programs: Figma, Asana, Slack, Jira, Microsoft Office Suite